我觉得爸爸希望我们走他的老路
I think dad want us to pick up where he left off.
救人猎魔
Saving people, hunting things...
延续家族事业
The family business.
我们得传承他的遗志
We have to carry out his legacy.
决定因素在于血统
It's a bloodline.
你有这样的血统
It's in your blood,
你父亲有这样的血统  这是你们家族的血统
Your father's blood, your family's blood.
-我喜欢约翰  -是吗
- I like that John kid. - You do?
是的  我认为你们俩注定是一对
Yeah, I think you two were meant to be.
是的  约翰和玛丽・温彻斯特的结合
Yeah, the union of John and Mary Winchester --
天造的一对  最优先的安排
Very big deal upstairs, top priority arrangement.
是你撮合了我们的父母
Are you saying that you fixed-up our parents?
命令说的很清楚
The orders were very clear.
你和萨姆必须出生
You and Sam needed to be born.
你们的父母是命中注定的
Your parents were just meant to be.
这本书
This book.
这是爸爸最宝贵的财产
This is dad's single most valuable possession.
他关于邪魔的全部知识都在里面
Everything he knows about every evil thing is in here.
他把这书留给了我们
And he's passed it on to us.
你说爸爸救过多少人
How many people do you think dad saved?
那是他的遗产
That's his legacy.
我们得继续下去
So we got to keep going.
伊利诺伊州  诺玛  1958年
伙计
Hey, sport.
抱歉
Sorry about that.
你去哪
Where are you going?
去工作
Work.
走之前来看看你
I just wanted to check on you before I left.
那是什么  爸爸
What's that, pops?
有一天  我会告诉你的
One day, I'll tell you all about it.
现在乖乖睡吧
Now get some shut-eye.
明早见
See you first thing in the morning.
晚安  儿子
Good night, son.
晚上好  先生
Good evening, sir.
乔茜
Josie.
我不知道上课这么正式
No one told me this initiation was a formal affair.
总得有人提升点品味  是吧  亨利
Well, someone had to class up the joint, right, Henry?
可不是嘛
Ain't that the truth?
难的部分都过去了
The hard part's over, right?
我们成功了
We made it.
桑兹小姐
Ms. Sands?
[咒语]
Secura tibi facias libertate.
Servire, te rogamus, audi nos!
亨利
Henry.
别让阿比顿拿到这个
Do not let Abbadon get it.
这不可能
That's impossible!
怎么会
How?
[咒语]
Kah-nee-lah...
Poo-goh.
[咒语]
Kah-nee-lah...
Poo-goh.
[咒语]
Kah-nee-lah...
Poo-goh.
谁是约翰・温彻斯特
Which of you is John Winchester?
凶鬼恶灵
第八季 第十二集
时光飞逝
拜托了  时间紧迫
Please, time is of the essence!
你们谁是约翰・温彻斯特
Which of you is John Winchester?
都不是
Uh, neither.
这不可能
That's impossible.
那绝对
That's absolutely...
我哪里做错了
What did I do wrong?
先生  你是谁
Who the hell are you, mister?
别烦我  我得想想
Not now. I'm thinking.
别这样
Please.
我保证你们没必要动粗
I can assure you there's no need for violence.
你们肯定有谁认识约翰・温彻斯特
One of you must know John Winchester.
这样吧
I'll tell you what --
如果我们中谁从你家壁柜里掉出来
When one of us falls out of your closet,
随便你提问
then you can ask the questions.
好吧  抱歉
Yes, my apologies.
先生  你非得用手按着我吗
Is it absolutely essential, sir, that you keep your hands on me?
谢谢
Thank you.
先生们
Gentlemen,
因为我完全不能解释
in the absence of any and all other explanations,
恐怕这是一场不可思议的可怕的误会
I'm afraid this has been a marvelous, tragic misunderstanding.
我这就走
I'll be on my way.
你休想
That's not happening.
情况紧急
There are things of grave importance.
我没时间应付你们这种人
I do not have time to deal with the likes of you.
哪都别想去  邦德
You're not going anywhere, 007...
先交待清楚
...till we get some answers.
他怎么做到的
How did he do that?
开我心呢
You got to be kidding me!
2013年
2013.
天呐
My god.
看来玛雅人说错了
Guess the mayans were wrong.
眼光不错啊
Nice taste in wheels.
是你的吧
Yours, I presume?
还用圣水
And there with the holy water.
他没问题
He's clean.
这我也能告诉你
I could have told you that.
你要是不想挨打
Yeah, well, you can start by telling us everything
就老实说吧
before I beat it out of you.
我想你们是无法理解的
I'm quite certain this is all beyond your understanding,
你这装老大的猴子
my alpha-male-monkey friend.
动用武力也不能帮你理解
And violence will not help you comprehend this any easier.
我告诉你我理解什么
Let me tell you what I understand!
有个混球从我衣柜里跌出来说要找我爸
Some asshat pops out of my closet asking about my dad,
还砸了我的车窗
smashes up my ride.
你说我为什么不对你动粗
So why am I not getting violent, again?
约翰・温彻斯特是你爸爸
John Winchester is your father?
怎么回事
What is that?
天呐
Oh, my God.
怎么了
What?
快跑
Run!
亨利
Henry.
傻小子  你忘记锁门了
Silly man, you forgot to lock the door.
不过咒语一直不是你的强项嘛
But then spells never were your best subject, were they?
乖乖地把我要的东西交出来
Why don't you be a doll and give me what I want?
我保证给你和你的朋友个干净的了断
And I promise to kill you and your friends here quickly.
我不能那么做
You know I can't do that.
你没那么坚强  亨利
You're not a fighter, Henry.
乔茜
Josie.
我知道你还在
I know you're still in there.
你得抵抗她
You must fight this.
乔茜略感不适
I'm afraid Josie's indisposed, pet.
所以只有你和我了
It looks like it's just you and me.
哪能这么对待一位女士
Well, that is no way to treat a lady.
快走
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
你没事吧  女士
You okay, lady?
你在干什么
What the hell are you doing?
告诉我你都看到了什么
Show me what you've seen.
谢谢
Thank you.
对了  我要退房
By the way, I'm checking out.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
没事
Yes, I will be.
只是一般我经历的冒险
It's just all the adventures I enjoy
都是书上读来的
are usually of the literary nature.
你吐也吐完了
Yeah, well, now that you're done blowing chunks,
能告诉我们那个复古美女是谁吗
you want to tell us who Betty Crocker was?
阿比顿
Abbadon.
她是个恶魔
She's a demon.
必须的
No kidding.
她哪来的
Where'd she come from?
你是哪来的
Where'd you come from?
她来自地狱
She's from hell.
我来自伊利诺伊  诺玛
I'm from Normal, Illinois --
1958年
1958.
扯淡吧你
Yeah, right.
真的
Seriously?
从汽车旅馆的壁柜里穿越时空
Dude's time traveling through motel-room closets?
我们就沦落到这个地步了
That's what we've come to?
如果你们能带我去见约翰
If you could just take me to John,
一切误会肯定都能澄清了
we could clear all this up, I'm sure.
我说了  那是不可能的
I've told you that's not gonna happen.
为什么
Why not?
因为他死了
Because he's dead!
不
No.
这与你何干
What's it to you?
一切
Everything.
我是他爸爸
I'm his father.
他驾照上写着
Driver's license says
他是伊利诺伊诺玛的亨利・温彻斯特
he's Henry Winchester from Normal, Illinois.
他知道爸爸的生日
He knows dad's birthday,
还有他出生的地方
the exact place where he was born.
伙计  那是我们爷爷
Dude, that's our grandfather.
我只是想说别急着跟他套近乎
I'm just saying before we break out the warm and toasties,
别忘了那个书虫
let's not forget that, uh, H.G. Wells over there
在爸爸小时候就抛妻弃子
left dad high and dry when he was a kid.
或许他没有呢
But maybe he didn't run out on dad --
或许不是故意的
I mean, not on purpose.
或许他是穿越来了这里
Maybe he time-traveled here
然后就没能回去
and, I don't know, got stuck.
不论如何  爸爸讨厌那混蛋
Yeah, well, either way, dad hated the son of a bitch.
那爸爸是怎么弥补的呢
And dad made up for that how?
他就是年度最佳父亲了吗
By being father of the year?
给你
Here you go.
谢谢
Thanks.
爸爸虽然也有毛病
Look, dad had his issues, okay,
但他从没抛弃过我们
But he was always there for us.
我最讨厌穿越了
I freaking hate time-travel, man.
你还好吗
How you doing?
没事
I'll be fine.
毕竟  不管怎样
After all, despite everything,
我刚刚认识了我的孙子
I've just met my grandsons, haven't I?
亨利・温彻斯特
Henry Winchester.
很荣幸认识你
It's a pleasure.
萨姆
Sam.
你好
Hello, Sam.
吃吧
Dinner.
这位是迪恩
This is Dean.
嗯
Right.
真是令人感动啊
Well, this has been touching.
我们来想想怎么给你收拾烂摊子吧
How about we figure out how to clean up your mess, huh?
阿比顿
Abbadon.
没错
Yes.
我们必须阻止她
She must be stopped.
我捅她的时候她怎么没死
And how come she didn't die when I stabbed her?
因为一般的刀具伤不了恶魔
Because demons can't be killed by run-of-the-mill cutlery.
至少
At the very least,
也得是用一把库尔德人的古弑魔刀
you'd need an ancient demon-killing knife of the Kurds.
这就是弑魔刀
That's what this is.
你哪弄来的
Where'd you get that?
一个恶魔给我的
Demon gave it to me.
这事我们干过很多次了
We've been around this block so many times.
你用来穿越的那个传送门还是什么的
Now, that portal or whatever it was you came through --
还是开启的吗
Is it still open?
我看不会
I highly doubt it.
怎么了
Why?
我在想如果我们杀不了这个阿比顿
I'm just thinking if we can't kill this Abbadon...
或许可以送她回家
Maybe we can shove her back where she came from.
你怎么做到的
How did you do it?
是个血印
It's a blood sigil.
血让我找到自己的血脉
Blood leads to blood.
或者他们的近亲
Or their next of kin.
但是阿比顿也过来了
But Abbadon came through it, also, right?
你能再做一次血印吗
So can you create this blood sigil again?
我的血
My blood,
一片天使羽毛
an angel feather,
龙之泪
tears of a dragon,
一小撮时之沙
a pinch of the sands of time --
这些都是必需品
I-I would need those and...
还得给我的灵魂一周的充电时间
at least a week for my soul to recharge,
但可以说是能做到的
but, yes, it's possible.
你借用灵魂之力才到这儿的
You tapped the power of your soul to get here?
我以为只有天使才能做到
I thought only angels could do that.
你们应该知道的
You should know this.
你俩是什么级别的
What level are you two?
级别
What level?
知识的级别
Level of knowledge.
你们是记录者吧
You're men of letters, correct?
我对偶像组合有点生疏了
I'm a little rusty on my boy bands.
记什么
Men of what?
记录者
Men of letters,
就像你们的父亲  教你知识的人
like your father, who taught you our ways.
我们的父亲教我们怎么猎魔
Our father taught us how to be hunters.
不会的
You're not.
你们是猎人
Are you? Hunters?
可猎人
Well, hunters are...
猎人只是粗人啊
Hunters are apes.
你们应该是
You're supposed to --
你们是传人
You're legacies.
什么的传人
Legacies of what?
这是怎么回事
What's going on here?
不
No.
好吧  这让人受启发
All right, well, this was enlightening.
咱们走吧
Let's hit the road, huh?
给他点时间  迪恩
Give him a minute, Dean.
我们刚刚开了四个小时
We just spent four hours driving, okay?
他这一路上就知道盯着窗外
All he did was stare out the window
还让我们放老歌
and request Pat Boone on the radio.
我够耐心了
He had his time.
这只是表象
It's just a facade,
让敌人相信我们搬去了别处
a way to rook our enemies into believing we are housed elsewhere.
行了  少装神秘了
Okay, enough with the decoder talk.
快告诉我们什么记录者是怎么回事
How about you tell us what this whole men-of-letters business is,
否则你就自己解决吧
or you're on your own.
这不管你们的事
It's none of your concern.
怎么  就因为我们是猎人
Why, because we're hunters?
你对我们有什么意见
What do you have against us?
除了不假思索
Aside from the unthinking, unwashed,
不问清楚就动手
shoot-first-and-don't-bother-to- ask-questions-later part,
还真没什么
not much, really.
你别忘了
You know what? Wait a second.
我们也是约翰的孩子
We're also John's children.
你们不止如此
You're more than that, actually.
我父亲和他的父亲都是记录者
My father and his father before him were both men of letters.
约翰和你们俩也该是的
As John and you two should have been.
我们是导师
We're preceptors,
旁观者
beholders,
记录一切凡人不理解的事件
chroniclers of all that which man does not understand.
我们的发现只告诉几个可以信任的猎人
We share our findings with a few trusted hunters --
那些强中强手
The very elite.
剩下的就交给他们
They do the rest.
那你就是我们绝地武士的尤达大师
So you're like Yodas to our Jedis.
算了  你迟早会知道的
Never mind. You'll get there.
好吧  如果你们那么厉害
Okay, but if you guys were such a big deal,
那我们  还有我们认识的所有人
then why haven't we -- or anyone we know --
都没听说过你们
ever heard of you?
阿比顿
Abbadon.
亨利  告诉我
Henry. Why?
她为什么这么做
Why'd she do it?
我想是为了这个
I think for this.
好吧  那是什么
Okay, what's that?
我也不知道
I wish I knew.
阿比顿在我最后一课的时候袭击了我们
Abbadon attacked us the night of my final initiation.
本来我会知道一切秘密
All secrets were to be revealed then.
让我理理
Let me get this straight.
你穿越时空来保护一样
You traveled through time to protect something
你也不知道是什么的东西
that does you don't know what
不让它被一个你不了解的恶魔偷走
from a demon that you know nothing about?
真好
Good.
把你的对讲机给我
Hand me your... walkie-talkie.
-你是说我的手机吗  -那更好
- You mean my phone? - Even better.
接线员  给我接D457
Operator, I need delta 457.
你是想打给谁
Who are you not calling?
我们的应急号码
Our emergency number.
是嘛  现在不是那个号了
Yeah. Not anymore.
他们不可能都没了
They can't all be gone.
肯定还有长者在
There must be another elder out there
能帮我们想办法打败阿比顿
who can help us figure out how to stop Abbadon
告诉我们怎么处理盒子
and what to do with the box.
能借用一下你的电脑吗
Can we hijack your computer for a hot second?
这屋子里哪能装下电脑
Like you could fit a computer in this room.
没问题
Sure.
谢谢
Thanks.
-你来  -好嘞
- Sam. - Yep.
好吧
All right, um...
说个名字  任何一个
Give me a name -- anybody who, uh,
那晚可能在场的长者
might have been there that night -- one of those elders.
大卫・阿克斯
Um...Ackers, David.
拉里・加农
Larry Ganem.
泰德
Um, Ted --
找到了
Okay, here it is.
1958年8月12日
Um, August 12, 1958.
绅士俱乐部发生可怕的火灾
A tragic fire at a Gentlemen's Club.
地址是盖恩斯街242号
Uh, 242 Gaines Street.
那就是这里
This is 242 Gaines Street...
但是灾难不是大火
But that was no fire.
拉里・加农  大卫・阿克斯
Larry Ganem, David Ackers,
泰德・鲍恩和大阿尔伯特
Ted Bowen, and Albert Magnus --
全部死亡
All deceased.
大阿尔伯特
Albert Magnus.
你朋友
He a friend of yours?
比那还好
Even better.
这些都是我的朋友
These were my friends,
我的导师
my mentors,
抵挡阿比顿最后的防线
our last defense against the Abbadons of the world.
那是你朋友大阿尔伯特
Here's your buddy Albert Magnus.
他叫大阿尔伯特
Albertus Magnus.
他并不是我朋友
And he was hardly a buddy.
他是中世纪最伟大的炼金术士
He was the greatest alchemist of the middle ages.
那他怎么埋在这里了
Okay, so why is he buried here?
他没有
He's not.
我们需要隐姓埋名时就用他的名字做假名
His was the alias we'd use when going incognito.
我想有人特意把他的名字放在那篇报道里
I believe someone planted his name in that article...
这样如果有记录者来追查
So that if a man of letters came looking for answers,
他就会知道有蹊跷
he'd know something was amiss.
那么有人想让你来找这座坟墓
So someone wanted you to come to this grave.
关键是他的目的
The question is why.
这是什么
What is this?
我们的徽章
Our crest.
水瓶星
The aquarian star,
代表了强大的魔法和力量
representing great magic and power.
据说在亚特兰蒂斯的大门上也有
They say it stood at the gates of Atlantis itself.
所有人的墓碑上都有  除了他
It's on all the tombstones except for this one --
拉里・加农
Uh, Larry Ganem.
这是海地人的标志  "对死人诉说"
The Haitian symbol for speaking to the dead.
这就是密文
This is the message.
你们挖过坟吗
You boys ever exhume a body?
我真喜欢你的装饰
Love what you've done with the place.
来错日子了
Wrong night.
《魔女嘉莉》周日放映
"Carrie" Screening's on sunday.
不过你服装真好看
I dig your costume, though.
你要干什么
What are you doing?
告诉我你都看到了什么
Show me what you've seen.
能借用一下你的电脑吗
Can we hijack your computer?
说个名字
Give me a name.
大卫・阿克斯
Ackers, David.
拉里・加农
Larry Ganem.
-可怕的火灾  -不是大火
- Tragic fire. - That was no fire.
大阿尔伯特
Albert Magnus.
谢啦
Thanks.
麦克林郡讣告记录
别伤害我
Please don't hurt me!
魔鬼逼我的
我喜欢你的衬衫
I like your top.
你想告诉我咱们是怎么走到这一步的吗
You want to tell me how we got stuck doing this?
一战老兵拉里
Hey, was, uh, Larry a world war I vet?
不是
No.
那这家伙是谁
Well, then, who's the stiff?
不清楚
No idea.
凯里三世托马斯・J 上校
Captain Thomas J. Carey iii.
你认识他吗
That mean anything to you?
某人想让你看到这
Well, somebody wanted you to see this,
也许那个某人就是拉里
so maybe that somebody is Larry.
也许他在袭击中幸存
So, what, maybe he, uh, survives the attack,
并且以这个人的身份隐匿起来
and hides out with this guy's identity?
好吧
Okay.
那我们还等什么
What are we waiting for, then?
把坑填上  我们上路吧
Cover this up. Let's be on our way.
这是什么  我听过这个调
What is that? I know that tune.
"时光飞逝"
"As time goes by."
卡萨布兰卡市: 摩洛哥西北部港市
希望我没说错  这个来自卡萨布兰卡
I hope so. It's from "Casablanca."
对
Right.
爸爸时不时的会哼这首歌
Dad used to whistle it from time to time.
你父亲一天晚上在路边的汽车影院
Your father saw "Abbott and costello meet the mummy"
看了《两傻大战木乃伊》
at the drive-in one night.
把他吓得到魂都破了
It scared the beeswax out of him.
所以我给他了一个播放这首歌的音乐盒
So I got him this little music box that played that song
帮助他晚上入睡
to help him sleep at night.
非常管用
It worked like a charm.
很难相信
Wow, it's hard to believe
爸爸也曾经怕过某些东西
Dad was ever scared of anything.
据县志记载
According to county records,
汤姆・凯里住在堪萨斯州的黎巴嫩
Tom Carey lives in Lebanon, Kansas,
而且是个快乐的127岁的老人
and is a very happy 127-year-old.
咱们打个盹
I say we get some shut-eye,
明天一大早就行动
head over first thing in the morning.
等一下  听听这个
Wait, wait, wait. Listen to this.
根据爸爸的日志记载
According to dad's journal,
他曾经拷问过的一个恶魔说
he once tortured a demon that said
自己是为阿比顿卖命的
he made his bones working for Abbadon,
结果那个恶魔是一个地狱骑士
who, it turns out, is a knight of hell.
那是什么意思
What does that even mean?
地狱骑士是路西法亲手挑选的
Knights of hell are hand-picked by Lucifer himself.
他们是第一代堕落天使  第一代恶魔
They are of the first-fallen, first-born demons.
所以非常纯种  非常强大
So very pure, very strong.
传说中说大天使把他们都杀了
Legend has it that archangels had killed all of them,
但如同我们所见  事实并非如此
which, as we have witnessed, is not the case.
也许她是仅剩的一位
Unless she's the last of her kind.
-你说这是你父亲的  -是的
- You say that belonged to your father? - Yeah.
我能看看吗
May I?
这是一本猎人的日志
It's a hunter's journal.
你们记录者也写日志吧
I assume men of letters...you use journals, too?
我本打算写的
I intended to.
我上课的前一天邮购了一本
I sent away for one the day before my initiation.
实际上是从我名字的的首字母上判断的
As a matter of fact, judging by my initials here,
我相信就是这本
this one, I believe.
这曾经是你的
That was yours?
它一定是在...
It must have arrived after...
我开始感觉
I'm beginning to gather
我这次没能回去  对不对
I don't make it back from this time, do I?
我们也不确定
We don't know for sure.
我们只知道从那之后爸爸再也没见过你
All we do know is that dad never saw you again.
你觉得我出什么事了
What did he think happened to me?
他以为你把他遗弃了
He thought you ran out on him.
约翰是一个传人
John was a legacy.
我本应该教他记录的方法
I was supposed to teach him the ways of the letters.
他学的方式略有不同
Well, he learned things a little differently.
什么方式
How?
艰难坎坷的方式
The hard way.
在寂寞的童年中长大
Surviving a lonely childhood,
还有恶心的战争
a stinking war...
不料自己的妻子被恶魔抓走
Only to get married and have his wife taken by a demon...
不久就死在恶魔手中
and later killed by one himself.
他回回都遇到不公平的命运
That man got a bum rap around every turn.
但你知道吗
But you know what?
他坚持走了下去
He kept going.
而且到最后
And in the end,
他所做的好事远比做的坏事多
he did a hell of a lot more good than he did bad.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我真希望我当时在他身旁
I wish I had been there for him.
是啊  但你不觉得现在说这话有点晚了
Yeah, it's a little late for that now, don't you think?
这是我们为了伟大事业所做出的牺牲
It's the price we pay for upholding great responsibility.
这你懂的
We know that.
你的责任在于你的家人
Your responsibility was to your family,
不是什么美其名的读书俱乐部
Not some glorified book club!
我是一名传人  我别无选择
I was a legacy. I had no choice.
是啊  你一直都是这么说
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that.
醒醒
Wake up!
怎么了  怎么了
What? What?!
亨利  他走了
Henry -- he's gone.
-他去哪了  -不知道
- Where is he? - No idea.
他就留了张字条说他要去搞定一切
He just left a note saying he was gonna fix everything.
或者说搞砸一切
Yeah, or screw it all up.
好吧
All right.
欢迎
Satnam.
欢迎  旅行者
Welcome, traveler.
有什么可以帮忙的
What can I help you with?
我想要一滴龙的眼泪
I can use a tear of a dragon
少量时间之沙
and a pinch of the sands of time,
但不用包起来了
but don't bother wrapping it up.
我现在就要用
I'll be using it right away.
我们这里不卖那些东西
We don't carry those things here.
但我推荐你用卡瓦根
But can I interest you in some kava root?
治焦虑有效
It's great for anxiety.
你的窗户上  是猎魔者的标记
In your window -- hunters' signs.
我知道你是谁和你是干什么的
I know who you are and what you are.
现在把我的东西给我  我好上路
Now give me what I need so I can be on my way.
我同意
I agree.
你是该上路了  陌生人
You should be going, stranger.
我明白
I understand.
你不认识我
You don't know me,
所以你不愿卖给我
so you're reluctant to sell to me.
好吧
Fine.
但在我走之前
But please let me purchase some chamomile
麻烦卖给我一些甘菊治失眠
for my restless nights before I go.
[咒语]
Bah-rah-gah-doh.
睡个好觉
Sleep well.
现在知道他说"搞定一切"是什么意思了
Now we know what he meant by "Fix everything."
什么
What?
他撬开车箱  偷走一片天使羽毛
He broke in to the trunk, stole an angel feather.
我猜他又要
I'm guessing he's gonna whip up
再来一次血咒语
another one of those blood spells
把自己当成马蒂・麦夫莱飞回到50年代
and Marty Mcfly himself back to the 1950s.
马蒂・麦夫莱  电影《回到未来》主角
可以穿越时空
去干什么呢
To do what?
在地狱领主来之前阻止她吗
Stop abbadon before she strikes?
或者抓着爸爸开溜
Or grab dad and haul ass.
听着  关键是他就要这么做了
Look, point is he's doing it.
怎么做
How?
他还需要两样成分才能完成咒语
He still needs two ingredients for the spell.
除非
Unless...
除非这附近有卖巫术品的
Unless there's some place nearby that sells real hoodoo.
我给盖思打个电话
I'll call Garth.
所有部门  星相漫画屋疑似杀人案  地点
All units, possible homicide at astro comics. Location...
星相漫画屋疑似杀人案  1人死亡
-看呐  -怎么了
- Hey. - Hmm?
刚刚好  星相漫画屋一人死亡
It just hit the wires -- one dead at astro comics.
-阿比顿吗  -应该是
- Abbadon? - Yeah, has to be.
好吧  她接近了
Okay, so she's close.
我去找亨利  你找拉里
I'll go find Henry. You find Larry.
想办法杀掉这小妞
Figure out how to kill this chick.
这么说  亨利死了
So, Henry is dead.
我一直肯定他活下来了
I was so sure that -- that he had survived.
是啊  像我说的
Yes, well, um, like I said --
我找到了他的日记
I found his journal and was hoping
希望你能填补上空白
you could fill in the gaps
告诉我1958年那晚
and explain to me what happened
发生了什么事
that night in 1958.
没什么
It doesn't matter.
都过去了  我们都过去了
They're gone. We're gone.
可阿比顿没有
But Abbadon is not.
阿比顿是被雇用的
Abbadon was a hired gun.
那晚她杀了我们所有人
She killed us all that one night.
除了你
Everyone but you.
她没看到我
She blinded me.
我的幸存是个奇迹
It's a miracle I survived.
没事  亲爱的
It's okay, dear.
但她没得到她想要的东西
But she did not get what she came for.
那个盒子
The box.
听着  阿比顿来了
Listen, Abbadon is here,
她想要这东西
and she wants this thing.
所以我要得知道关于它的一切
So I need to know everything there is to know about it.
盒子里有一把钥匙
In the box is the key
通往所有的事物  卷轴  咒语
to every object, scroll, spell,
几千年来收集的所有东西
ever collected for thousands of years
都有一个地方
under one roof.
那是凶鬼恶灵的母窖
It is the supernatural mother lode.
[咒语]
Poo-goh.
Kah-nee-lah....
亨利  等等
Henry, wait!
我必须冒这个险
This is a risk I have to take.
你要是死了怎么办
And what if you die, huh?
谁说你就能在这一跳中活下来
Who said you'll even survive a jump?
你不能理解我看完约翰的日记后
You cannot begin to understand how I felt
是什么感受
after reading John's journal.
我觉得我能
Oh, I think I can.
我看过的次数超出你的想象
See, I've read that thing more times than you can imagine,
每次都会刺痛我
and it hurts every time.
或许是这样  但让他失望的不是你
Maybe so, but you didn't let him down!
是我  就像你说的
I did! Just like you said!
-我说的不对  -不
- Well, I was wrong. - No!
你说的没错
No, you were right.
我准备回到过去
And I'm going to go back
给他应得的生活
and give him the life he deserves,
而不是被迫选择的生活
not the one he was forced to live.
如果不是命中注定呢
What if it's not meant to be?
那就变成命中注定
Then it will be!
你怎能如此确定
How can you be so sure?
因为就应该这样做
Because it's the right thing to do!
我能解救他  阻止阿比顿
I can save him and stop Abbadon!
怎么做
How?
回到她攻击的一小时前
By going back an hour before she attacks
做些准备
and making preparations.
那样做  你会改变过去
If you do that and you change the past,
我和萨姆可能会消失
me and Sam might cease to exist!
我知道时间线很微妙
I'm aware that time is a delicate mistress,
但我愿意赌一把
but I'm willing to bet on this being for the best.
我明白这不是你想象中的完美结局
I understand that this is not your idea of a happy ending, okay,
还有你很失望  我和萨姆
and that you're disappointed that me and Sam
都是喘气的猎人
are mouth-breathing hunters.
但你知道吗  我们阻止了天启
But you know what? We stopped the Apocalypse.
如果我的计划能够实现
If this works the way I planned,
就根本不会有天启存在了
there will never be an Apocalypse to stop.
那么
So...
阿比顿想要钥匙
Abbadon wants the key
那样她就能拿到手了
so she can get her hands on it.
你能想象出她得到之后会干什么吗
Can you imagine what she would do with that?
那我们怎么才能阻止她
So, how do we stop her?
怎样才能阻止阿比顿
How do we stop Abbadon?
没办法
You don't.
如果你知道钥匙的下落
If you know where the key is,
把钥匙带到这个地点
then take it to these coordinates.
扔进去
Throw it in.
把大门永远关闭
Shut the door forever.
然后离开
And walk away.
等等  为什么我要那样做
Wait, w-why would I do that?
因为那是世界上最安全的地方
Because it is the safest place on earth,
能挡住所有恶魔
warded against any evil ever created.
没有任何东西能闯入
It is impervious to any entry,
除非有钥匙
except the key.
好  那样的话所有知识都会
Right, but then all that knowledge would be --
都会永远的丢失
would be lost and gone forever.
那就是我们必须付出的代价
And that is the price we have to pay
以免知识落入阿比顿手中
for keeping it away from ASbbadon.
你  的确有钥匙  是吗
You do... have the key, don't you?
我没有
I don't, um...
不过  我兄弟
But, uh, my brother...
我兄弟有
...my brother does.
没礼貌
How rude.
你还没喝完你的茶呢  萨姆
You haven't finished your tea, Sam.
阿比顿
Abbadon.
这些年不好过啊  拉里
The years have not been kind, Larry.
萨姆
Sammy?
不是
No.
比他性感多了
Much sexier.
再猜
Try again.
-阿比顿  -好孩子
- Abbadon. - Good boy.
听好了
Now listen up --
我想做一个老式的交易
I want to make a good, old-fashioned horse trade.
亨利和钥匙  换你兄弟
Henry and the key for your brother.
不然他就得死
Or he dies.
听清了吗
Am I clear?
清清楚楚
Crystal.
去拉里家的路上  有一座炼油厂
On the road to Larry's, there's a processing plant.
别让我等你
Don't keep me waiting.
阿比顿抓住萨姆了吗
Abbadon has Sam?
她想让我用你和钥匙来换萨姆的命
She wants to trade you and the key for Sam's life.
如果我能回到过去  这些都不会发生
If I could just go back, stop this all from happening.
如果你回不去呢
And what if you can't?
我不能冒险  现在萨姆命悬一线
I can't take that risk -- not with Sammy on the hook now.
我不能放弃我的儿子  迪恩
I can't abandon my son, Dean!
不能再次放弃了
Not again!
我必须这么做  抱歉
I need to do this. I'm sorry.
[咒语]
Kah-nee-lah...poo-goh.
我也很抱歉
Well, I'm sorry, too.
很抱歉
Sorry about that.
不  你没觉得抱歉
No, you're not.
从我们一见面你就想打晕我
You've wanted to do that since we met.
亨利  你得明白一件事
Henry, you need to understand something.
我爸爸死的时候  我救不了他
When my dad died, I couldn't save him...
不管我多想救他
...no matter how bad I wanted to.
我绝不会让这样的事情发生在萨姆身上
I never want that to happen to Sam...ever.
即使只有一丝救他的机会
If there's a chance that I can save him,
我要这么做
I'm gonna do it.
他是我弟弟  他是我仅有的家人
He's my brother. He's the only family I got.
迪恩  别这么做
Don't do it, Dean.
现在太晚了
Too late for that now.
这就是你们猎人的毛病
That's the problem with you hunters.
你们都目光短浅
You're all short-sighted.
是啊  至少我们不会灭绝
Yeah, at least we're not extinct.
阿比顿
Abbadon!
我会让亨利拿着盒子过去
I'll send Henry here over with the box.
你也要交出萨姆  不许耍手段
You do the same with Sam. No tricks.
我只对亨利和钥匙感兴趣
My only interest is Henry and the key.
你们俩可以离开
You two are free to go.
你可以自己走过去
You can do this standing,
否则你就得爬过去
or you can do it crawling.
自己决定
Your call.
亨利  抱歉
Henry, I'm sorry.
算了吧
Save it.
迪恩  不要这样  这计划真的不好
Don't do this, Dean. This is a bad idea.
闭嘴  我们走
Shut your mouth. Let's go.
走吧
Come on.
我们说好了的
We had a deal!
惊喜吧
Surprise.
我说谎了
I lied.
-亨利  -等下
- Henry! - Wait. Wait.
你不是唯一一个说谎的
You're not the only one.
我要这么做
I'm gonna do it.
他是我弟弟  他是我唯一的家人
He's my brother. He's the only family I got.
那么你有什么想法呢
So, what are you thinking?
你能拖住阿比顿吗
Can you slow Abbadon down?
如果你可以  剩下的就交给我了
Because if you can, I'll do the rest.
漂亮的一枪
Whoo! What a blast.
现在  快把盒子给我
Now, give me the box.
盒子在哪
Where is it?!
好吧
Okay.
我们可以来硬的了
We can do this the hard way.
我为什么不能动了
Why am I stuck?!
把恶魔陷阱刻在子弹上
A devil's trap carved into the bullet.
你得靠近点才行
You're gonna have to get close.
靠近意味着场面可能会变得很难看
And "close" means it could get ugly.
我知道  但是为了血脉必须如此
I know. But you do that for blood.
你还是没能杀死我
You still didn't kill me.
是啊  但是你会希望我们刚刚杀了你
No, but you'll wish we did.
你身体里的恶魔陷阱
The demon trap in your noggin
只是为了困住你
is gonna keep you from smoking out.
我们要把你碎尸万段
We're gonna cut you into little steaks
然后再把你的尸体埋入水泥
and bury each strip under cement.
你也许是不死之身  但是你会希望一死百了
You might not be dead, but you'll wish you were.
我们成功了
We did it.
不  是你成功了
No, you did it.
亨利  对你这种书呆子来说  干得很漂亮
For a bookworm, that wasn't bad, Henry.
抱歉之前对于你们是猎人的事说了很难听的话
I'm sorry I judged you two so harshly for being hunters.
我应该更懂的
I should have known better.
懂什么
About?
你们也是温彻斯特家的人
You're also Winchesters.
只要我们还活着
As long as we're alive,
就会有希望
there's always hope.
作为男人  我不了解我的儿子
I didn't know my son as a man,
但是见到了你们俩
but having met you two...
我知道我会为他引以为傲
I know I would have been proud of him.
H・温彻斯特
我现在懂了
I get it now.
什么
Hmm?
丘比特说的
What cupid said
天堂费尽心机撮合老爸老妈
about heaven busting ass to get mom and dad together.
温彻斯特家和坎贝尔家
The Winchesters and the Campbells --
智者和勇者
The brains and the brawn.
我很高兴你这么想
Well, I'm glad you see it.
我们的家谱  我看到的都是死者
All I see in our family tree is a whole lot of dead.
我...
Hey, I, uh...
在亨利的钱包里找到了这个
Found this in Henry's wallet.
老爸看起来很高兴
Dad looks happy.
这大概会让你希望他是知道真相的吧
Kind of makes you wish he knew the truth, huh?
那么多年  一直以为他的老爸丢弃了他
I mean, all those years thinking his old man ditched
实际上他却来到了这里救了我们
when the poor son of a bitch really came here and saved our bacon.
该死的时间穿梭啊
Freaking time-travel, man.
你觉得这会让一切变得不同吗
You think it would have made a difference?
什么
What?
老爸
Dad.
如果他有父亲陪伴他
If he'd had his own father around.
他要如何抚养我们吗
What, in how he raised us?
小萨姆  他尽到全力了
Sammy, he did the best he could.
我知道  我知道
I know that. I-I do.
他们都尽力了
They all did.
那地方还存在的可能性有多大呢
What are the chances that place is still standing?
我想  我们总得试一试
A chance we've got to take, I guess.
毕竟  我们也是传人啊  不是吗
I mean, we are legacies, right?